Guide to the Cable 13 Videotapes, 1976-2009 UA.09.13.0008
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Accession UA2016-0027, 1976-2009; 2
  - Interview w/ Al Goldstein - SCREW Mag., undated (Box 101, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-1027)
    Other notes: Editor of SCREW Magazine
  - Beyond Boundaries-Symposium, undated (Box 102, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-1028)
    Cable13 tape number: Part 1 (copy)
  - "Neuron Fever" Entry for Kammerer Award, undated (Box 102, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-1029)
    Program Length: 15mins; Other notes: David Pratt
  - The Powers That Be, undated (Box 103, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-1030)
    Program Length: 6mins; Other notes: Rebecca Pryce, Shea Pepper
  - Chuck Davis and the AADE, undated (Box 56, Video-cassette UA09130008-VHS-0059)
    Program Length: 7mins; Other notes: Chuck Davis and the African-American Dance Ensemble (dub copy) by Ian T. McGloin
  - Ivy Tower - 1st Daze, undated (Box 92, Video-cassette UA09130008-VHS-0060)
  - Widespread Panic's "Postcard", undated (Box 94, Video-cassette UA09130008-VHS-0061)
    Other notes: a Dionysus production, by Tal Thompson
  - "Tricolor", "Checking Out", "Harder", "The Lion's Tale", undated (Box 95, Video-cassette UA09130008-VHS-0062)
    Program Length: 42mins; Other notes: "Tricolor" Nick Vivion, 7:43, "Checking Out" Andrew Fazekas, 3:15, "Harder" Gabriel Morgan/Sam Morgan, 15:45, "The Lion's Tale" Charaine Stanford, 15:00
  - Kammerer Prize Video Entries, undated (Box 95, Video-cassette UA09130008-VHS-0063)
    Other notes: 6 films
  - Gothic Fall, undated (Box 95, Video-cassette UA09130008-VHS-0064)
    Other notes: Dir: Mike Mitchell
  - Gothic Fall, undated (Box 95, Video-cassette UA09130008-VHS-0065)
  - Gothic Fall, undated (Box 95, Video-cassette UA09130008-VHS-0066)
  - Learning Resources Network: Hostages, undated (Box 95, Video-cassette UA09130008-VHS-0067)
  - Learning Resources Network: Hostages, undated (Box 97, Video-cassette UA09130008-VHS-0068)
  - Learning Resources Network: Our Bomb, undated (Box 97, Video-cassette UA09130008-VHS-0069)
  - Learning Resources Network: Hostages, undated (Box 97, Video-cassette UA09130008-VHS-0070)
  - "Talk About the Passion" & "The Potential Within", undated (Box 97, Video-cassette UA09130008-VHS-0071)
    Program Length: 38mins
  - Chuck Davis and the AADE by Ian McGloin, undated (Box 97, Video-cassette UA09130008-VHS-0072)
  - Chuck Davis and the AADE by Ian McGloin, undated (Box 97, Video-cassette UA09130008-VHS-0073)
  - Chuck Davis and the AADE by Ian McGloin, undated (Box 97, Video-cassette UA09130008-VHS-0074)
  - The Phil Giodano Jazz Quartet, undated (Box 97, Video-cassette UA09130008-VHS-0075)
    Other notes: Selections: 1. That's It 2. Just Friends 3. Ceora 4. Tenderly
  - Sleight of Hand - Backers Audition, undated (Box 97, Video-cassette UA09130008-VHS-0076)
  - 1492 WTVD, 2 News shows "Reflections", undated (Box 103, Video-cassette UA09130008-VHS-0077)
  - Union Promo, undated (Box 103, Video-cassette UA09130008-VHS-0078)
  - "Bombay Though a Video Eyeball", undated (Box 103, Video-cassette UA09130008-VHS-0079)
    Other notes: by Josh Gibson
  - Kammerer Prize Videos, undated (Box 103, Video-cassette UA09130008-VHS-0080)
    Other notes: "Flakes" 2min, "Morning People" 15mins, "Bombay Through a Video Eyeball" 6mins, "Dead Man's Hand" 6mins, "Class Project" 6mins
  - "Incarnadine", undated (Box 103, Video-cassette UA09130008-VHS-0081)
    Other notes: directed by Alanna Thain
  - Proud Space: Durham's Black Barbers Remember, undated (Box 103, Video-cassette UA09130008-VHS-0082)
    Other notes: Jordan Sable
  - Kammerer Prize Videos, undated (Box 103, Video-cassette UA09130008-VHS-0083)
  - Kammerer Prize Videos, undated (Box 103, Video-cassette UA09130008-VHS-0084)
  - The College TV Network Operator Reel, undated (Box 103, Video-cassette UA09130008-VHS-0085)
    Program Length: 3mins10secs
  - Duke University Harassment Policy, undated (Box 103, Video-cassette UA09130008-VHS-0086)
    Other notes: VDI